Princeton Football Films Collection, 1935-2012(bulk 1935-1990): Finding Aid AC297
University Archives
- Princeton Freshman (Frosh) Football Film Reels, 1922-2001; 671 items
  - Princeton/Wilkes, 9/10/82 - DEF. #2, 1982; 1 item (Item 368)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85- Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1985; 1 item (Item 369)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85- Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1985; 1 item (Item 370)
  - Princeton/Glassboro, 10/21/85 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1985; 1 item (Item 371)
  - Princeton vs. Army #2, undated; 1 item (Item 372)
  - Princeton vs. Army #1, undated; 1 item (Item 373)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85 - DEF. - PASS SKELETON, 1985; 1 item (Item 374)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85 - DEF. - 1 on 1, 1985; 1 item (Item 375)
  - Princeton vs. Army #4, undated; 1 item (Item 376)
  - Princeton/E. Strouds - DEF. #2, undated; 1 item (Item 377)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/7/79 - OFF. #2, 1979; 1 item (Item 378)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/7/79 - DEF. #2, 1979; 1 item (Item 379)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/7/79 - DEF. #1, 1979; 1 item (Item 380)
  - Princeton/Glassboro, 10/21/85 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1985; 1 item (Item 381)
  - Princeton/East Stroud., 10/14/85 - Reel #5, DEF.2, 1985; 1 item (Item 382)
  - Princeton/East Stroud., 10/14/85 - Reel #5, DEF.1, 1985; 1 item (Item 383)
  - Princeton/East Stroud., 10/14/85 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1985; 1 item (Item 384)
  - Princeton/Glassboro, 10/21/85 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1985; 1 item (Item 385)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85 - Reel #5 OFF. 1, 1985; 1 item (Item 386)
  - Princeton/East Stroud., 10/14/85 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1985; 1 item (Item 387)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85 - Reel #5, 'Kicks', 1985; 1 item (Item 388)
  - Princeton/Wilkes, 9/10/82 - OFF #1, 1982; 1 item (Item 389)
  - Princeton/Wilkes, 9/10/82 - 'Kicks', 1982; 1 item (Item 390)
  - Princeton/Wilkes, 9/10/82 - OFF #1, 1982; 1 item (Item 391)
  - Princeton vs. Brown #3, undated; 1 item (Item 392)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 9/24/84 - OFF. #1, 1984; 1 item (Item 393)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 9/24/84 - OFF. #2, 1984; 1 item (Item 394)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 9/24/84 - DEF. #1, 1984; 1 item (Item 395)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 9/24/84 - DEF. #2, 1984; 1 item (Item 396)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth - DEF. #2, 1977; 1 item (Item 397)
  - Squad Scrimmage Show - 3+ Long, Short Yard, Goal Line (2nd Part), undated; 1 item (Item 398)
  - Princeton/Penn. - Roll #1, Half- Defense, 1973; 1 item (Item 399)
  - Princeton/Penn. - 'Kicks', undated; 1 item (Item 400)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia #2, undated; 1 item (Item 401)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia #2, undated; 1 item (Item 402)
  - Princeton vs. Delaware #2, undated; 1 item (Item 403)
  - Princeton vs. Navy #3, undated; 1 item (Item 404)
  - Princeton vs. Delaware #3, undated; 1 item (Item 405)
  - Princeton vs. Delaware #4, undated; 1 item (Item 406)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia #3, undated; 1 item (Item 407)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #3, undated; 1 item (Item 408)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #2, undated; 1 item (Item 409)
  - Princeton vs. Brown #2, undated; 1 item (Item 410)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell #1, undated; 1 item (Item 411)
  - Princeton vs. Navy #4, undated; 1 item (Item 412)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell Fr. - 'Kicks', undated; 1 item (Item 413)
  - Princeton vs. Delaware #1, undated; 1 item (Item 414)
  - Princeton vs. Navy #2, undated; 1 item (Item 415)
  - Princeton B/Dartmouth, 10/2/83 - 'Kicks', 1983; 1 item (Item 416)
  - Princeton F (17)/Dartmouth (0), 10/2/83 - DEF #1, 1983; 1 item (Item 417)
  - Princeton/Glassboro St. #3, 9/24/79, 1979; 1 item (Item 418)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 9/24/84 - 'Kicks', 1984; 1 item (Item 419)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #1, undated; 1 item (Item 420)
  - Princeton B/Dartmouth, 10/2/83 - OFF #1, 1983; 1 item (Item 421)
  - Princeton B/Dartmouth, 10/2/83 - OFF #2, 1983; 1 item (Item 422)
  - Princeton F (17)/Dartmouth (0), 10/2/83 - DEF #2, 1983; 1 item (Item 423)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell #2, undated; 1 item (Item 424)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #1, undated; 1 item (Item 425)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #3, undated; 1 item (Item 426)
  - Princeton vs. Dartmouth (?), undated; 1 item (Item 427)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 428)
  - Perim. Tech., Tiger Tech., Tackling, undated; 1 item (Item 429)
  - Return to Jim Luck: GA Tech - Atlanta, GA, 26-27 Power, undated; 1 item (Item 430)
  - Princeton Fr. - 2nd Quarter, undated; 1 item (Item 431)
  - Princeton Fr. - Print #2, undated; 1 item (Item 432)
  - Princeton Fr. - Roll #3, undated; 1 item (Item 433)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 434)
  - Princeton - Roll #1, undated; 1 item (Item 435)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia #2, undated; 1 item (Item 436)
  - Kick Off Coerage - Punt Returns, undated; 1 item (Item 437)
  - Princeton vs. Yale - #2, undated; 1 item (Item 438)
  - Princeton vs. Yale - #1, undated; 1 item (Item 439)
  - Princeton vs. Yale - #3, undated; 1 item (Item 440)
  - Princeton vs. Lafayette - #3, undated; 1 item (Item 441)
  - Princeton vs. Lafayette - #2, undated; 1 item (Item 442)
  - Princeton vs. Lafayette - #1, undated; 1 item (Item 443)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell - #4, undated; 1 item (Item 444)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell - #3, undated; 1 item (Item 445)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell - #2, undated; 1 item (Item 446)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard - #4, undated; 1 item (Item 447)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 448)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 449)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 450)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 451)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 452)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 453)
  - Princeton Flex Program, undated; 1 item (Item 454)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 455)
  - Princeton/Virginia #4, undated; 1 item (Item 456)
  - Princeton Fr. - 4th Quarter, undated; 1 item (Item 457)
  - Princeton - Roll #4, undated; 1 item (Item 458)
  - Princeton - Roll #5, undated; 1 item (Item 459)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 460)
  - Princeton Frosh - Roll #2, undated; 1 item (Item 461)
  - Princeton Frosh - Roll #3, undated; 1 item (Item 462)
  - Princeton - Roll #3, undated; 1 item (Item 463)
  - Bowdoin #2, undated; 1 item (Item 464)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85 - OFF. PASS SKELETON, 1985; 1 item (Item 465)
  - Princeton (44)/Glassboro (6), 10/21/85 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1985; 1 item (Item 466)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1985; 1 item (Item 467)
  - Princeton (44)/Glassboro (6), 10/21/85 - Reel #5, 'Kicks', 1985; 1 item (Item 468)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85 - Goal Line, 1985; 1 item (Item 469)
  - Princeton/Springfield, 9/14/85 - OFF. 1 ON 1, 1985; 1 item (Item 470)
  - Princeton/East Stroud., 10/14/85 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1985; 1 item (Item 471)
  - Princeton vs. Lafayette - #4, undated; 1 item (Item 472)
  - Princeton vs. Navy #1, undated; 1 item (Item 473)
  - Princeton vs. Brown #4, undated; 1 item (Item 474)
  - Princeton vs. Brown #1, undated; 1 item (Item 475)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 9/7/90 - Reel #3, DEF. #1 and #2, 1990; 1 item (Item 476)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 9/7/90, 1990; 1 item (Item 477)
  - Bowdoin #4, 9/19/87, 1 item (Item 478)
  - Bowdoin (19) vs. Tufts (24), 10/22/88 - Reel #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 479)
  - Bowdoin (19) vs. Tufts (24), 10/22/88 - Reel #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 480)
  - Bowdoin (19) vs. Tufts (24), 10/22/88 - Reel #3, 1988; 1 item (Item 481)
  - Bowdoin (10) vs. Bates (6), 11/5/88 - Reel #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 482)
  - Bowdoin (10) vs. Bates (6), 11/5/88 - Reel #3, 1988; 1 item (Item 483)
  - Bowdoin (10) vs. Bates (6), 11/5/88 - Reel #4, 1988; 1 item (Item 484)
  - Bowdoin (20) vs. Bates (25), 10/29/88 - Reel #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 485)
  - Bowdoin (20) vs. Nor. (16), 9/18/87 - Reel #3, 1987; 1 item (Item 486)
  - Princeton Fr. - 3 Quarter, undated; 1 item (Item 487)
  - Bootleg PASS/ Luck, undated; 1 item (Item 488)
  - Princeton vs. Yale #3, undated; 1 item (Item 489)
  - Princeton vs. Delaware/VNF - Daylight #4 (130 Ft.), undated; 1 item (Item 490)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia/VNF -Daylight #4 (160 Ft.), undated; 1 item (Item 491)
  - Princeton vs. (?) #4, undated; 1 item (Item 492)
  - Princeton vs. Brown #4, undated; 1 item (Item 493)
  - Princeton vs. Brown #1, undated; 1 item (Item 494)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell #3, undated; 1 item (Item 495)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia #1, undated; 1 item (Item 496)
  - Princeton vs. Navy #1, undated; 1 item (Item 497)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 498)
  - Princeton vs. Yale #1, undated; 1 item (Item 499)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 500)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell #1, undated; 1 item (Item 501)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #2, undated; 1 item (Item 502)
  - Princeton vs. Brown #2, undated; 1 item (Item 503)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #2 (?), undated; 1 item (Item 504)
  - Princeton vs. Dartmouth #3, undated; 1 item (Item 505)
  - Bowdoin (6)/Williams (36) #4, 10/17/64, 1964; 1 item (Item 506)
  - Amherst (19)/Bow (18) #1, 10/10/64, 1964; 1 item (Item 507)
  - Wesleyan (0)/Bow (14) #1, 10/3/64, 1964; 1 item (Item 508)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 509)
  - Yale '47 - Reel #4, Copy #3, undated; 1 item (Item 510)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 511)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 512)
  - Princeton Frosh - Reel #1, undated; 1 item (Item 513)
  - Princeton Fr., Print #1, undated; 1 item (Item 514)
  - Princeton Fr. - 1 Quarter, undated; 1 item (Item 515)
  - Princeton Frosh - Reel #2, undated; 1 item (Item 516)
  - Princeton vs. Navy #2, undated; 1 item (Item 517)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell #4 (20 Test), undated; 1 item (Item 518)
  - Princeton vs. Dartmouth #2, undated; 1 item (Item 519)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #4 (240), undated; 1 item (Item 520)
  - Princeton vs. Dartmouth #2, undated; 1 item (Item 521)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia #4, undated; 1 item (Item 522)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia #3, undated; 1 item (Item 523)
  - Brown (or Penn.?) vs. Princeton University - OFF. #2, undated; 1 item (Item 524)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #1, undated; 1 item (Item 525)
  - Princeton vs. Lafayette #1, undated; 1 item (Item 526)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #3, undated; 1 item (Item 527)
  - Princeton vs. Harvard #2, undated; 1 item (Item 528)
  - Princeton vs. Yale #2, undated; 1 item (Item 529)
  - Princeton/Brown #3, Reel #4, undated; 1 item (Item 530)
  - Princeton/Brown #4, Reel #4, undated; 1 item (Item 531)
  - Princeton/Brown #4, Reel #2, undated; 1 item (Item 532)
  - Princeton vs. Maine #4, 1/7/01, 2001; 1 item (Item 533)
  - Princeton vs. Maine #3, 1/7/01, 2001; 1 item (Item 534)
  - Princeton vs. Maine #1, 1/7/01, 2001; 1 item (Item 535)
  - Princeton vs. Maine #2, 1/7/01, 2001; 1 item (Item 536)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 537)
  - Princeton vs. Yale (Freshman) - 1st Half Offense, undated; 1 item (Item 538)
  - Princeton vs. Yale (Freshman) - 2nd Half Defense, undated; 1 item (Item 539)
  - Columbia vs. Princeton University - Offense #2, undated; 1 item (Item 540)
  - 2nd Half: Maine Offense vs. U.Mass Defense, 10/18/86, 1986; 1 item (Item 541)
  - 1st Half: Maine Offense vs. U.Mass Defense, 10/18/86, 1986; 1 item (Item 542)
  - Yale F. vs. Princeton - 3rd Quarter, undated; 1 item (Item 543)
  - Princeton Freshman vs. Yale Freshman - 2nd Quarter, undated; 1 item (Item 544)
  - Princeton vs. Yale (Freshman) - 2nd Half Offense, undated; 1 item (Item 545)
  - For Princeton: Columbia Freshman Print - Reel #2, undated; 1 item (Item 546)
  - FROSH: Princeton/Penn., 11/1/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 547)
  - FROSH: Princeton/Penn., 11/1/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 548)
  - Princeton vs. Lafayette #4, undated; 1 item (Item 549)
  - Princeton vs. Lafayette #2, undated; 1 item (Item 550)
  - Princeton vs. Lafayette #3, undated; 1 item (Item 551)
  - Princeton vs. Army #2, undated; 1 item (Item 552)
  - Princeton vs. Yale #3, undated; 1 item (Item 553)
  - Princeton/Lafayette, 9/2/89 - Reel #4, DEF. #1, 1989; 1 item (Item 554)
  - Princeton/Lafayette, 9/2/89 - Reel #4, 'Kicks' (Print), 1989; 1 item (Item 555)
  - Princeton/Lafayette, 9/2/89 - Reel #4, 'Kicks' (Orig.), 1989; 1 item (Item 556)
  - Princeton/Lafayette, 9/2/89 - Reel #4, OFF. (Print), 1989; 1 item (Item 557)
  - Princeton/Lafayette, 9/2/89 - Reel #4, OFF. #1 (Orig.), 1989; 1 item (Item 558)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 10/28/83 - DEF. #2, 1983; 1 item (Item 559)
  - Team Def. vs. Run, undated; 1 item (Item 560)
  - Pass Rush, undated; 1 item (Item 561)
  - Endplay, undated; 1 item (Item 562)
  - Pass 90, Pass 70, undated; 1 item (Item 563)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 564)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 565)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 566)
  - Harvard - Frosh, undated; 1 item (Item 567)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 568)
  - Princeton vs. Columbia #3, undated; 1 item (Item 569)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell #1, undated; 1 item (Item 570)
  - Princeton Freshman vs. Yale Freshman - 4th Quarter, undated; 1 item (Item 571)
  - Princeton vs. Brown #3, undated; 1 item (Item 572)
  - Princeton vs. Cornell #4, undated; 1 item (Item 573)
  - Princeton DEF., undated; 1 item (Item 574)
  - Princeton vs. Delaware #1, undated; 1 item (Item 575)
  - Princeton vs. Delaware #2, undated; 1 item (Item 576)
  - Princeton vs. Delaware #3, undated; 1 item (Item 577)
  - Passes, undated; 1 item (Item 578)
  - HB Trap, undated; 1 item (Item 579)
  - Princeton (6)/Bowdoin (3) - WMS 51 #2, undated; 1 item (Item 581)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 582)
  - Defensive Backs, Tiger Bracket, undated; 1 item (Item 583)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 584)
  - Princeton Football 1975 - Hi-Lite 1975, 1 item (Item 585)
  - Princeton Football 1974 - Hi-Lite 1974, 1 item (Item 586)
  - Princeton Football 1975 - Hi-Lite 1975 #2, 1 item (Item 587)
  - Princeton Football 1975 - Hi-Lite 1975 #3, 1 item (Item 588)
  - Princeton Football 1975 - Hi-Lite 1975 #4 (?), 1 item (Item 589)
  - College Football '78: A Year of Suprises?, 1978; 1 item (Item 590)
  - Princeton: A Search for Answers (Print #3), 1973; 1 item (Item 591)
  - Princeton Football 1972, 1 item (Item 592)
  - Princeton Football 1968 - '68 Football Highlights, 1 item (Item 593)
  - Princeton Football 1966 - Hi-Lites 1966, 1 item (Item 594)
  - Princeton Football 1971, 1 item (Item 595)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 596)
  - College Football '77: A New Season, 1977; 1 item (Item 597)
  - Princeton Football 1970, 1 item (Item 598)
  - Yale vs. Princeton, undated; 1 item (Item 599)
  - Alumni Council: Princeton/Yale 1981 Special, 1 item (Item 600)
  - Princeton/Yale 1981 (Film 2), 1 item (Item 601)
  - Bad Film, undated; 1 item (Item 602)
  - Alumni Council Presents 'Princeton Football Highlights 1963' (Print #2), 1 item (Item 603)
  - The Orange Key (Print 4), undated; 1 item (Item 604)
  - The Orange Key (Print 6), undated; 1 item (Item 605)
  - Alumni Council Presents 'Princeton Football Highlights 1964', undated; 1 item (Item 606)
  - Walt Smith, undated; 1 item (Item 607)
  - Harvard/Princeton to 8, 1965; 1 item (Item 608)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 609)
  - 1951 vs. Lafayette - 3rd Quarter (Single Wing), undated; 1 item (Item 610)
  - Wesleyan (0)/Bowdoin (14), 10/3/1964 - Reel #3, 1 item (Item 611)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 612)
  - WMS '51 #1, Protestant Radio Comm., 1951; 1 item (Item 613)
  - Weslyn '51, 1951; 1 item (Item 614)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 615)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 616)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 617)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 618)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 619)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 620)
  - Rugby?, undated; 1 item (Item 621)
  - Princeton vs Harvard, 1961; 1 item (Item 622)
  - Dartmouth III, 1946; 1 item (Item 623)
  - Dartmouth Reel I, undated; 1 item (Item 624)
  - Dartmouth Reel II, 1950; 1 item (Item 625)
  - Dartmouth Reel III, 1950; 1 item (Item 626)
  - Dartmouth, 1951; 1 item (Item 627)
  - Dartmouth, Reel 4, 1951; 1 item (Item 628)
  - Princeton vs Dartmouth, Nov 24, 1956; 1 item (Item 629)
  - Lafayette vs Princeton, undated; 1 item (Item 630)
  - Lafayette Reel I, 1949; 1 item (Item 631)
  - Lafayette, Reel 4, 1951; 1 item (Item 632)
  - Princeton vs. Lehigh, 1960; 1 item (Item 633)
  - Princeton vs Brown 3-2, undated; 1 item (Item 634)
  - Brown vs Princeton, 1951; 1 item (Item 635)
  - Princeton 6-5, undated; 1 item (Item 636)
  - Maine I, 1950; 1 item (Item 637)
  - Princeton Football Highlights, Yale-Dartmouth, 1960; 1 item (Item 638)
  - Colby, 1951; 1 item (Item 639)
  - Colby, 1951; 1 item (Item 640)
  - Colby, 1951; 1 item (Item 641)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 642)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 643)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 644)
  - Rutgers OFF 1, undated; 1 item (Item 645)
  - Rutgers OFF 2, undated; 1 item (Item 646)
  - DIPIPI, undated; 1 item (Item 647)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 648)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 649)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 650)
  - No description, udated; 1 item (Item 651)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 652)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 653)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 654)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 655)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 656)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 657)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 658)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 659)
  - Columbia, 1962; 1 item (Item 660)
  - Princeton vs Penn, 2nd Period, Oct 30, 1976; 1 item (Item 661)
  - PUFH, 1969; 1 item (Item 662)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 663)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 664)
  - Basketball, undated; 1 item (Item 665)
  - No description, 1932; 1 item (Item 666)
  - Football, old P-Rade, campus scenes, 1922-1923; 1 item (Item 667)
  - No description, undated; 1 item (Item 668)
  - PUFH, 1949, 1950, 1951; 1 item (Item 669)
  - Football, 1966; 1 item (Item 670)
  - PUFH, 1973; 1 item (Item 671)
  - Basketball, 1975; 1 item (Item 672)